trashbilling.com 2011-01-07

# TrashBilling.com - Privacy Policy

## TRASHBILLING.COM PRIVACY POLICY

This policy describes the ways we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it.

#### How we collect information about you 

When you access the TrashBilling.com website, we collect your IP address and standard web log information, such as your browser type and the pages you accessed on our website; that information is retained in our log files. We receive your most recent contact information and payment history from your hauler. When making a payment or initiating or altering auto-pay we also collect contact information (name, address, phone, and email) and financial information.

Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store results when you respond to a survey.

Any information we collect about you, your computer, or other access devices may be used for fraud prevention purposes.

#### How we use cookies

When you access our website, we may place small data files called "cookies" on your computer in order to insure proper and secure operation of the website.

We send a "session cookie" to your computer when you log in to your account. This type of cookie helps us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages on our site during the same session, so that we don't need to ask you for your password on each page. Once you log out or close your browser, this cookie expires and no longer has any effect.

We encode our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them. You are free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of TrashBilling.com.

#### How we protect and store personal information

Throughout this policy, we use the term "personal information" to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been anonymized so that it does not identify a specific user.

If you wish to further secure your account, you may create a password of your choosing, which will not be made available to your hauler.

We store and process your personal information on our computers in the US, and we protect it by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable US federal and state regulations. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption, we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files, and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities.

#### How we use the personal information we collect

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a secure, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. We may use your personal information to:

  * provide the services and customer support you request; 
  * process transactions and send notices about your transactions; 
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; 
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Service; 
  * customize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website; or 
  * compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties. 

Neither TrashBilling.com nor its parent companies, subsidiaries, or other affiliates will use customer information obtained from TrashBilling.com to market products and services, other than TrashBilling.com, to you.

#### How we share personal information with haulers

To process your payments, we need to share some of your personal information with the hauler that you are paying. All of your contact information and payment history is provided to your hauler. Credit card numbers and bank account routing/account numbers are provided to your hauler only in the event that you register for auto-pay services. If an attempt to pay your hauler fails, or is later invalidated, we may provide your hauler with details of the unsuccessful payment. To facilitate dispute resolutions, we may provide a user with the hauler's address so that questions or issues can be addressed to the hauler.

Neither your hauler nor its parent companies, subsidiaries, or other affiliates will use customer information obtained through TrashBilling.com to market products and services, other than those provided by the hauler.

We will not disclose your credit card number or bank account number to anyone, except with your express permission (e.g., signing up for Auto-pay) or if we are required to do so to comply with federal or state law, a subpoena or other legal process.

#### How we share personal information with other parties

We may share your personal information with:

  * Banking partners, as required by credit card association rules, NACHA rules or state or federal laws 
  * Companies that we plan to merge with or that acquire TrashBilling.com or its parent company (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information could be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.) 
  * Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when 
    * we are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order or similar legal procedure; 
    * we need to do so to comply with law; or 
    * we believe in good faith that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of our Terms of Service. 
  * Other third parties with your consent or direction to do so. 

TrashBilling.com will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes and only shares your personal information with third parties as described in this policy.

#### How you can access or change your personal information

You can review your personal information at any time by logging in to your account with your web ID number; to change any of your personal information, please contact your hauler directly.

#### How you can contact us about privacy questions

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact us by writing to us at Ivy Computer, Inc., Attn: Privacy Department, 2933 Waterbury-Stowe Rd., Waterbury Center, Vermont 05677.
